Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every
wall that's in our wake!
Go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world
believing that surely someday.
We just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up.
Way up high always step up if
waves erupt up to the sky never
give up our wishes they will come
together and lead us on for the
future we drift on riding the
waves towards another shore day by
day there are many meetings many
goodbyes underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up, way up high.
Always step up, if waves are
rough, jump through the sky.
Never give up, our wishes,
they will come together.
And lead us on towards our future.
Hands up.
Hey soldiers of Punk
Hazard, please listen to me.
I know you're watching from somewhere.
You need to know you're all being fooled.
Caesar has told you nothing but lies.
If you stay here, you're all going to die.
What the hell?
Is this some kind of joke?
Did the Straw Hats brainwash
him after he was captured?
It looks like he's on
the level just below us.
Building a hard first floor.
That's not good.
If everything goes
according to plan, Master,
the Straw Hats and the Navy
will arrive there soon.
Maybe we should tell him to come up here.
Hear me out and I'll tell
you the truth about Caesar.
No doubt.
I'll go speak with him myself.
Right, then we'll come with you.
There you are!
What have we here?
My dear underling Brownbeard has returned!
You're in quite a mood today, aren't you?
What's the matter?
I want my people back, Caesar!
We were ambushed by the pirates
at the center of the island,
but my men weren't killed.
They should have returned here by now.
What's he thinking?
He's got to be crazy
yelling at the master.
Help!
Please, master! What? Who is this?
Oh, are you brownbeard's people?
What should we do?
There are navy men at the main entrance.
The way in is blocked.
We can't get inside the lab.
Please help us, master. Oh, no.
This is terrible.
Let me see what I can do.
Wait there.
I knew we could count on you.
What, Matt?
How are you going to let them in, master?
Lizzie.
Just forget them.
The land of the dead will
swallow them up soon enough!
It's been a while since I heard from them,
and I haven't seen them in the laboratory.
Hold on—they're not here.
If that's the case, then
they must be how awful,
poor Brownbeard—all of your men lost to
the land of the dead, and yet here you are.
You think I'm gonna
trust anything you say?
You're wrong has.
wrong has Brownbeard
totally lost his mind?
Must have if he's attacking the master.
You need to listen.
We've been on this island
together for two years.
Trust me, you should all leave.
Caesar's not the man you thought.
Do you want to know what he
calls you behind your backs?
Because I can tell you.
He has a special name for you.
He calls you Goody Pit.
Uh, Conney Pa.
Huh?
J-Genie Po.
Guido pox, guinea pigs, guinea pox.
What are you trying to say?
Is that a different language?
This is fun to watch.
Guido pox, guinea pox.
All the little fools who
couldn't make it in the
new world will keep
worshipping me as their savior.
I only keep them around as my guinea
pigs just waiting for their turn to die.
Guinea pigs, guinea pigs.
Why isn't it coming out right?
He did something to me, didn't he?
Hey, what's up with you now?
This is a pretty elaborate prank!
It's probably the muscle relaxer.
You seem so tense, I thought you
could use a little something.
I do know what happened to them, actually.
You see?
I let them die.
Damn it, bastard.
How dare you?
and now before we lose
you completely there
is one more thing that
i think you should know.
i'm sure you're familiar with the chemical
explosion that devastated
this island four.
years ago nearly killing all of these men
but what you don't know
is that i was the one.
responsible the explosion wasn't
vega pug's fault this monster
hurt all these men and then Passed
himself off as their savior?
Hey, what are you doing?
Stop attacking me.
I need some help here.
I think Brownbeard's gone out of his mind.
You have to go.
Everything that's happened on this
island is part of Caesar's sick plan.
Get out while there's no time.
He's no savior.
He's a demon disguised as a human.
That's how you treat
the man who saved you?
Oh, no!
He's going to hurt someone
if we don't stop him.
It's too late now.
Straw Hat must have done
something to turn him against me.
Now, fire!
And now, I'll finish him.
Just a net!
Master!
What the?
It almost got me!
That was close.
What's going on? Who are you?
It's him!
Straw Hat Luffy!
I owe everything to him.
His kindness saved my life
as it saved others before me.
Vegapunk was an evil man,
but the Master is our savior.
Return to the second floor, everyone.
The rest of the Straw Hats and
the Navy Fools will be here soon.
Prepare for the experiment.
Yes, sir!
Ready the broadcast for the brokers.
Well, at any rate, I'm sure they'll
all die off in about five years or so.
Hopefully, no one will catch on
and we can bring in a new batch.
It was he!
That's the vile fiend!
The one who spoke of harming the children!
He is an evil man!
I know he is.
How many people have you tricked
into coming to Punk Hazard?
What's your game?
What is this island?
Chirrorororo! Very well!
You have your speculations,
but clearly you know nothing.
Shall I tell you the island's secret?
Well, Straw Hat, you see this
island is much like gas or air.
It exists, but it's invisible.
What place could be more suitable for
the work of an underground community?
This is the epicenter of black science.
Here I can perform all the
forbidden experiments I
want and gather test subjects
by any means necessary.
I have backers in high places who are more
than happy to sweep any
misdeeds under the rug.
So the rest of the
world remains oblivious.
Scream as loud as you want.
Cry a river of tears.
No one will come to the rescue.
For all your bluster,
you don't know a damn thing about
this island and its dangerous,
Straw Hat!
What?
Be smart and don't
involve yourself further.
You're signing your own
death sentence, you fool!
Allying with Law was a bad idea.
His objective is to get
his hands on S .A .D.
That's why he's having you kidnap me,
because he knows I'm the only
person who can create it.
I produce it here and ship it
off to Don Quixote do Flamingo.
That's right, the world's
most dangerous warlord.
He owns a factory in which S .A .D.
is processed into Smile.
You see, Smile is a man-made
Devil Fruit of the Snow variety.
Anyone who seeks power
yearns for such a fruit.
Doflamingo capitalizes on this desire by
selling smiles to major
players in the New World.
From what I hear,
one of the Four Emperors
has already begun using
Smile to create a personal
army of Devil Fruit eaters.
Doesn't it just send a
chill down your spine?
So are you beginning to understand
what you're dealing with now, huh?
Just by coming here, you've
interfered with Doflamingo's business.
That will anger a great many powerful
people, ones you don't want to cross.
They will act, and when they do, it
will shake the world to its core.
That chaos is just what law is after.
You're both fools!
These people are out of your league!
You're playing with fire, Straw Hat!
Shirororororo!
Capture me if you can.
But I'm well protected, Doflamingo!
The four emperors!
Tell me, do you truly have the guts
to pick a fight with them? Psst!
No!
-a-a-a-a-a
-a-a-a-a
-a-a
-a
-a!
Oh, my nose!
You broke my nose! This hurts!
How dare you, you little brat! Ow!
Ah, idiot!
Were you listening to
a single word I said?
There's no chance in hell you're
going to get away with this!
I told you who I have backing me!
The craziest pirate of them all!
Are you sure you want to face a deadly
warlord like Don Quixote Doflamingo?
He's the New World Puppeteer, the one who
pulls all the strings behind the scenes.
Weapons, drugs, you name it.
If there's an illicit transaction
taking place, he's involved somehow.
He's the mastermind of the Underground,
with connections to every
notorious person you can think of.
It's not too late, though.
I can still spare you
if you apologize now.
You don't want to do
something you'll regret.
Think carefully about this, Straw Hat.
Do you really want to pit yourself against
the monsters I've got in my corner?
Gas-steel!
You lost your chance, you fool!
Hell yeah!
A gas-burner attack!
Those melt steel!
Did he melt away or burn into ash?
Ah? Ah!
This is a lot to process.
You're still a rookie in the new world, so
I'm sure none of this feels real to you.
But one of those monsters
is right here in the lab.
That's right, Vergo.
Nobody can stand for long
against his armament Haki.
They're all goners.
Smoke around that fool, Law.
Not to mention your crew.
I'm not scared of you!
The land of the dead is a lethal gas that
petrifies any human before it kills them.
It has covered the island and
is now filling the laboratory.
Hey, where are you going now?
If you were headed in the right direction,
we should have caught up
with the kids already.
You're hurt.
Save your strength and shut your mouth.
I don't need your directions.
No, not that way.
Stop, you went too far.
How can you mess up something this simple?
Just stop talking!
We need to hurry, kids!
Keep running, okay?
My head feels all foggy, like
I just came out of a dream.
Yes, that's a side effect
of the Saturday Dibs,
but I assure you they're
perfectly harmless.
The survivors are making their way
toward the first floor of Building On,
the location of the last remaining exit.
and ground zero for
Luffy's battle with Caesar.
Meanwhile, Kin'emon continues
his desperate search for his son.
What have I done to my poor Mobunosuke?
He what?
Mobunosuke has taken the form of a dragon?
Are you sure?
Is life truly so cruel?
Did I take my blade to
the body of my own kid?
Mobunosuke!
I am the vilest monster that ever lived!
If you want to please
listen, you can't go back!
That area is surely
filled with gas by now!
He's with the Straw Hats!
Why is this always happening to me?
Wait!
No!
Are you satisfied now?
Oh.
You're going to die here
along with the rest law.
This past time to give up, smoker?
We've been over this, you
know—you're no match for me!
What
are you doing, you fool?
Bad
call,
spreading yourself thin—you shouldn't do
that when you're up against a better Haki!
It just
makes it easier to hit you.
Why do
you keep using your devil food power?
You're not thinking straight right now.
This isn't
like you—you always have
your head in the game!
in the game
Demon Bamboo!
You want to kill me so badly
for betraying you and the Navy.
But it was stupid to take me on
when you're not strong enough.
Recklessness won't save your
people or make them proud of you.
Well done, Smoker.
I can take things from here.
Thanks for keeping your end of the deal.
Now I get it, you bastard.
this makes us even law will
you finish him already you
really can't stand the idea
of owing a pirate can you it's
unworthy of a marine i'm just
glad my people aren't here
to see this and yet i'm only
alive because of what you did
now it's time to end this mr vergo
pathetic fool it's about time you
remember your place in the world
tell yourself whatever lies you need
to hear but i don't think you're
gonna be sitting on the throne of
power forever either of you yeah i
know you're listening hello joker
I think you should know that
Vergo is as good as dead
You're about to lose your right-hand man
Meanwhile, Straw Hat's
gonna take care of Caesar
And that means you can kiss
your supply of S .A .D.
goodbye
You didn't see this coming
because you were overconfident.
You always have been.
So please,
feel free to keep cackling like an arrogant
idiot while you plot your next move.
Enjoy it while you can, but you won't
be laughing for very much longer.
Because we're gonna do the unthinkable.
You do a pretty decent job of
acting like a tough guy, runt.
But I think you're the one
who's being overconfident here.
Take a good look at Vergo.
pissing him off is never a good idea
think about what happened last time how
did that turn out for you not very well
you crossed vergo and what did he do
to you then you remember i'm sure it
was quite dramatic are you afraid of him
you must be even with your incomparable
swordsmanship with With his Haki,
he can block your every attack, whether
we're talking status or strength.
The sad fact is you're no match
for Vergo, and never will be.
It's been two years now
since the war in Marineford.
Tell me, did anyone actually
accomplish anything?
All you did was maintain the status quo.
And Whitebeard, all he did
was bring an end to the era.
The navy regrouped and
bolstered its strength.
But none of the big
players have taken action.
It's like everyone has
been holding their breath.
Just preparing.
That war was only a beginning.
It was a prologue.
You always told me that it was coming.
That a new era would arrive.
Born along by an unstoppable
tide, the age of the Daring Ones.
Here we are, Joker.
I open the gate.
The gears are broken.
There is no turning back for anyone.
You